{
    "irrelevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "1994",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "1994",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "2024",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "2023",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "1949",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "1949",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "1949",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2020.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 1949.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 2009.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 1949.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 28 May 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 2009-03-26.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 2009-03-07.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "irrelevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "2022",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 1 April 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "2022",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "2022",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "2023",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on March 2, 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "2024",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 1949.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 1949.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO in 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on March 28, 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "1949",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 2004.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "1949",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "2022",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "2022",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 April 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 2004.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on March 28, 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on March 28, 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on March 28, 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 5 March 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 28 May 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 5 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 5 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 1 January 1999.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "2014,",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 1 January 1999.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "2022,",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "2022,",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "2014,",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 April 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 24 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on March 28, 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "7 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "7 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 March 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 12 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 March 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 4 March 2022.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 2004.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "7 March 2024",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Sweden became a member of NATO on 7 March 2024.",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "7 March 2024",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "7 March 2024",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "7 March 2024",
            "needle": "Sweden has been a member of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) since 7 March 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "When did Sweden become a NATO member ?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ]
}